https://www.enterprisedataerasure.com/privacy-policy/

Home
| Privacy Policy
Extreme Protocol Solutions Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy only applies with respect to information Extreme Protocol Solutions collects from Web sites on which a direct hyperlink to this “Privacy Policy” is posted. It describes the way we handle information learned about you from your visit to our Web sites. Other Web sites (including those we link to) not owned or operated by or for us have different data processing practices for which we do not vouch or assume responsibility.
If you have any questions, comments, or requests regarding privacy, please send us an email at privacy@extremeprotocol.com.
Collection Of Information
We collect statistical information about you, such as the pages visited on EPS Web sites, unique URLs visited within our Web sites, the domains from which people visit our Web sites, browser type and IP address. Generally, we do not link such information to any of your contact information (such as name, email address or user name). Most of this information is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. Accepting the cookies used on our site does not give us access to your personal information, but we may use the cookies to identify your computer. We also collect personally identifiable information about you that you voluntarily submit to us, such as by filling out a form or survey, registering your email address with us or emailing us. We may also collect personal information from you at other points on our Web sites that state that personal information is being collected. Personally identifiable information that we collect from you may consist of your contact information, product purchase information or product usage information. We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children and do not knowingly market our products or services to children.
Disclosure Of Information
Unless we tell you otherwise, or unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy or required by law, we do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third parties. However, we might share your personally identifiable information and aggregated (non-personally identifiable) information with our affiliates, distributors and resellers if allowed to do so under applicable laws. The affiliated companies, distributors and resellers may be in the United States or in other parts of the world. When you submit personal information to us during your visit to our Web sites, we will let you know how you can (a) prevent our use of this information for marketing purposes or, (b) if we are required to do so under applicable laws, prevent the disclosure of this information to third parties for marketing purposes, if you so choose.
We could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or some or all of our assets could be acquired. If such a combination or acquisition occurs, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our Web site in the event we share with the merging or acquiring entity some or all of your personal information.
Use Of Information
We use personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information for our marketing and sales purposes, for Web site administration, and for such purposes as expressly stated when you provided your information. We will not use this information for other purposes, unless you consent to the new usage or if required or permitted by applicable law. Of course, if applicable, we do use personally identifiable information to perform the services for which such data was collected (i.e., if you sign up for an email newsletter, we will send the email newsletter to the address you provide us). If you want to opt-out of receiving communications you have expressly requested (such as e-mail newsletters), you may do so by selecting the “opt-out” or “unsubscribe” link in each email that you receive from us, by returning to the Web site where you originally submitted your information, if applicable, and following the opt-out instructions therein, by submitting an email message to privacy@extremeprotocol.com, or by using the online form entitled “Update Your Contact Information”.
Occasionally, we will send you e-mail communications with information, which may be useful to you, including information about our products and services or about offerings from affiliates or business partners. When you first provide us with your e-mail address, you will be given the option of not receiving any such e-mail communications. We will include instructions in our e-mail messages on how to unsubscribe if you later decide you do not want to receive any future e-mail communications. From time-to-time, our Web sites request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose the requested information. This information will be used for our marketing and sales purposes, for Web site administration and for such purposes as expressly stated in the survey or contest. Personal data given to us in one country may be transferred to a different country for the purpose of processing, data consolidation, storage and simplified customer information management, unless prohibited by applicable law.
Cookies And Other Collection Tools
When you view our Web sites or advertisements, we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our Web sites, to help you navigate a Web site as easily as possible. Cookies can help us to better understand how users use our Web sites, which in turn helps us focus our resources on features that are more popular with our users. If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our Web site, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies. If your browser permits, you can refuse a cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence or generally refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, but some parts of our Web sites, including the portion which is targeted for our registered customers, may not work properly in that case.
Security
We are committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, we have safeguards protecting the information we collect. If appropriate, we use authentication tools among other methods to protect your web-based personal information. Of course, there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet. E-mails you send us are not necessarily secure when they are transmitted to us. If your communication is sensitive or includes highly confidential information, you may want to provide it by post or via the telephone instead. When appropriate, we restrict the number of employees internally who can access such data and instruct such employees that the data is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and our internal policies.
